KASHISH GULATI

+91 8750856988 • kgulati100@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/kashish-gulati/

SUMMARY

Data Analyst with 3+ years of experience in data collection, manipulation and analysis using SQL, Python, and Advanced Excel. Carrying an avid interest in learning and exploring to build, evaluate and implement models to solve business problems across domains and contribute to the success of an organization.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology - ECE,

Bhagwan Parshuram Institute of Technology (GGSIPU)

CGPA: 8.24/10.0 2021

SKILLS

- Hands on experience on SQL for data querying and manipulation.
- Strong Data analysis and visualization skills using Python.
- · Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Excel, including data analysis, Macros, VBA, Stats and Pivots.
- Familiarity with statistical analysis and machine learning techniques.
- Excellent problem-solving and analytical abilities.
- · Strong communication and teamwork skills.

EXPERIENCE

Also Energy (Stem Inc.): Data Analyst

Sep 2021 - Present

- Conducting data analysis and creating meaningful reports and visualizations using SQL and Microsoft Excel to identify
 patterns and trends, and make data-driven recommendations to the stakeholders to support decision-making.
- Advance site configuration of Solar sites using Excel's data analysis and pivot reporting to manage the site efficiently.
 Calculating Energy savings, Demands and analyzing data for different types of batteries to aid customer's choice of battery for energy savings.
- Real-time tracking and reporting of solar and other renewable plants.
- MySQL Queries to fetch data from DataMart for troubleshooting the bills and optimizing battery's performance. Also developed live dashboard on Jira to actively track the process to increase its efficiency
- Co-led discovery, design, and implementation of new internal data verification process across fleet, leading to increased data reliability and accuracy.
- Development experience in MYSQL and Python to automate various processes across domains.
- · Experience in manipulating both structured and unstructured data through statistical/numerical languages.

Airport Authority of India: Internship

June 2019 - July 2019

- Gained exposure to air traffic control technologies, including radar, VOR, ILS, and other navigational aids.
- Studied the principles of VOR and ILS navigation systems and their role in ensuring safe and efficient aircraft operations.

PROJECTS

Weather And Travel Information App

April 2023 - May 2023

Develop an application that provides users with detailed weather information and travel recommendations for a specified city. The app should leverage multiple RESTful APIs, including a weather API and a travel API, to offer a holistic view of the destination.

Cardiovascular Disease Analysis

April 2023 - May 2023

Conducted a comprehensive analysis of a dataset comprising 70,000 patient records to identify the presence of cardiovascular disease. Leveraged Python libraries, including NumPy, SciPy, and Matplotlib, to perform data cleaning, processing, and exploration.